Guide to the Corcoran Gallery of Art and Corcoran College of Art + Design, Corcoran Gallery of Art rental records, 1961-1973 COR0003.1.RG
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Administration, 1961-1981; Series 2
  - Correspondence, 1958-1981; Series 2 Subseries 3
    - Art Rental Gallery Correspondence, 1964; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box RG3.1-1998.003, Folder 75)
    - Art Rental Gallery Correspondence, 1965; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box RG3.1-1998.003, Folder 76)
    - Art Rental Gallery Correspondence, 1966; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box RG3.1-1998.003, Folder 77)
    - Art Rental Gallery Correspondence, 1967; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box RG3.1-1998.003, Folder 78)
    - Art Rental Gallery Correspondence, 1968; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box RG3.1-1998.003, Folder 79)
    - Art Rental Gallery Correspondence, 1969; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box RG3.1-1998.003, Folder 80)
    - Art Rental Gallery Correspondence, 1970; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box RG3.1-1998.003, Folder 81)
    - Art Rental Gallery Correspondence, 1971; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box RG3.1-1998.003, Folder 82)
    - Art Rental Gallery Correspondence, 1972; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box RG3.1-1998.003, Folder 83)
    - Art Rental Gallery Correspondence, 1973; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box RG3.1-1998.003, Folder 84)
    - Art Rental Gallery Correspondence, 1974; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box RG3.1-1998.003, Folder 85)
    - Art Rental Gallery Correspondence, 1978; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box RG3.1-1998.003, Folder 86)
    - Art Rental Gallery Correspondence, 1981; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box RG3.1-1998.003, Folder 87)
  - Inventory and shipping lists, 1962-1974; Series 2 Subseries 4
    This subseries contains a listing of the ARG collection, a listing of ARG works in storage, a list of galleries and artists, and listings of art work to be picked up by shipping companies and returned to commercial galleries. Also included in this file is the office supply inventory and the list of reception supplies.
    - Inventory and Shipping Lists-ARG [Art Rental Gallery], 1962-1973; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.003, Folder 88)
  - Operating reports and procedures, 1962-1973; Series 2 Subseries 5
    This subseries contains the initial 1962 proposed operating procedure and estimate of initial expenses; information on the consignment process; the commission policy; contract revisions; volunteer procedures; reports on the history, goals and operating procedures of the ARG; and the ARG termination letter.
    - Operating Reports and Procedures-Art Rental Gallery, 1962-1972; Series 2 Subseries 5 (Box RG3.1-1998.003, Folder 89)
  - Rental procedures -- corporate and individual, 1962-1973; Series 2 Subseries 6
    This subseries contains the ARG rental policy for both corporations and individuals; the individual and corporate membership policies; and the rules and regulations governing the rental and purchase process.
    - ARG [Art Rental Gallery]-Rental Procedures Corporate and Individual, 1970-1975; Series 1 Subseries 6 (Box RG3.1-1998.003, Folder 90)
  - Financial reports, 1962, 1969-1971; Series 2 Subseries 7
    This subseries contains quarterly reports; the report of initial start-up expenses in 1962; various appropriations and budget requests; and the financial statement, from August 1958-July 1959, of the privately sponsored Art Rental Gallery that was the forerunner of the Corcoran ARG.
    - Financial Reports-Art Rental Gallery, 1959-1971; Series 2 Subseries 7 (Box RG3.1-1998.003, Folder 91)
  - Balance sheets and art rental accounts, 1964-1966; Series 2 Subseries 8
    This subseries is arranged alphabetically.
    This subseries contains individual and corporate accounts.
    - Balance Sheets/Art Rental Accounts, Series 2 Subseries 8 (Box RG3.1-1998.003, Folder 92)
  - Bills due, 1962-1967; Series 2 Subseries 9
    This subseries contains tally sheets with the name of the renter, the date the bill was sent, and the date the bill was paid.
    - Bills Due, 1962-1967; Series 2 Subseries 9 (Box RG3.1-1998.003, Folder 93)
  - Maintenance, repairs, framing, 1962-1973; Series 2 Subseries 10
    This subseries contains records of maintenance, such as cleaning, done on works that hung in the ARG; records of repairs to damages to art works incurred while rented out, or during shipping; and receipts and bills sent to artists and commercial galleries for framing done on works that hung in the ARG.
    - Maintenance, Repairs, Framing, 1971-1972; Series 2 Subseries 10 (Box RG3.1-1998.003, Folder 94)
  - Publicity and public relations, 1962-1973; Series 2 Subseries 11
    This subseries contains the Art Rental Gallery brochure; press releases touting the ARG; and drafts of public relations promotional material for various publications such as Town and Country.
    Five publicity photographs have been removed to the photograph file.
    - Publicity/Public Relations-ARG [Art Rental Gallery], 1962-1969; Series 2 Subseries 11 (Box RG3.1-1998.003, Folder 95)
  - Legal problems and suits, 1968-1971; Series 2 Subseries 12
    This subseries may contain materials with restricted content. All requests to use materials in this subseries must be reviewed and approved by the Public Services Librarian.
    This subseries contains information on the Robert Hamsley and Joan Guiles thefts. The file includes correspondence between the ARG, the ARG legal counsel, and the guilty parties concerning the theft of art work from the Rental Gallery. Also included are the attorneys' suggestions for changes in the rental agreement contract to prevent such thefts from being repeated.
    - Legal Problems/Suits-ARG [Art Rental Gallery], Series 2 Subseries 12 (Box RG3.1-1998.003, Folder 96)
  - Insurance, 1962-1973; Series 2 Subseries 13
    This subseries contains correspondence with the insurance agencies used by the Art Rental Gallery to insure the works of art that they had out on loan: records of the amounts of insurance required each month; and copies of policies, endorsements, and claims made. The ARG did business with two insurance firms, Holmes, Hart, and Ewing, and Huntington T. Block, both Aetna representatives.
    - Insurance, 1962 February-1962 September; Series 2 Subseries 13 (Box RG3.1-1998.003, Folder 97)
    - Insurance-Holmes and Hart, 1963-1964; Series 2 Subseries 13 (Box RG3.1-1998.003, Folder 98)
    - Insurance, 1965; Series 2 Subseries 13 (Box RG3.1-1998.003, Folder 99)
    - Insurance, 1966; Series 2 Subseries 13 (Box RG3.1-1998.003, Folder 100)
    - Insurance, 1967-1968; Series 2 Subseries 13 (Box RG3.1-1998.003, Folder 101)
    - Insurance, 1969-1970; Series 2 Subseries 13 (Box RG3.1-1998.003, Folder 102)
    - Insurance, 1971-1972; Series 2 Subseries 13 (Box RG3.1-1998.003, Folder 103)
    - Insurance, 1972-1973; Series 2 Subseries 13 (Box RG3.1-1998.003, Folder 104)
  - Sample forms, 1962-1973; Series 2 Subseries 14
    This subseries contains samples of the forms and form letters used in the ARG, and includes rental agreement, master contract, sales receipt, and rental receipt forms. Also included are form letters to artists announcing the sale of art work, and the termination letter sent to artists and commercial galleries upon the close of the ARG.
    - Forms (Sample)-Art Rental Gallery, Series 2 Subseries 14 (Box RG3.1-1998.003, Folder 105)
- Rental and sales, 1962-1981; Series 3
  Organized into 6 subseries: Rental applications, Rental agreements, Corporate rental agreements, Rental returns, Rental gallery income, and Rental gallery exibitions and sales.
  - Rental applications, 1962-1973; Series 3 Subseries 1
    This subseries contains members' applications to borrow from the ARG that were not attached to specific rental agreements, and include name, address, business, bank, charge accounts, and membership classification.
    - Rental Applications, 1964; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box RG3.1-1998.003, Folder 106)
    - Rental Applications, 1969; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box RG3.1-1998.003, Folder 107)
    - Rental Applications, 1970; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box RG3.1-1998.003, Folder 108)
    - Rental Applications, 1971-1973; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box RG3.1-1998.003, Folder 109)
  - Rental agreements, 1962-1973; Series 3 Subseries 2
    This subseries contains rental agreements. The information on the rental agreement includes name, address, phone number, consignment number, artists, title of art work, medium, price, rental fee, check/cash payment, due date, date returned, and all legal obligations of the lessee. Attached are receipts, relevant correspondence, and member rental applications.
    Arranged in numerical order, starting with 1 and running through 3999.
    - Rental Agreements 1-15, 1962 October; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box RG3.1-1998.003, Folder 110)
    - Rental Agreements 16-28, 1962 October- 1962 November; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box RG3.1-1998.003, Folder 111)
    - Rental Agreements 30-37 (26 and 27 void), 1962 November; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box RG3.1-1998.003, Folder 112)
    - Rental Agreements 39-49, 1962 November-1962 December; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box RG3.1-1998.003, Folder 113)
    - Rental Agreements 50-60, 1962 December; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box RG3.1-1998.003, Folder 114)
    - Rental Agreements 61-72, 1962 December-1963 January; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box RG3.1-1998.003, Folder 115)
    - Rental Agreements 75-89, 1963 January; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box RG3.1-1998.003, Folder 116)
    - Rental Agreements 90-104, 1963 January-1963 February; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box RG3.1-1998.003, Folder 117)
    - Rental Agreements 105-106, February 1963; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box RG3.1-1998.003, Folder 118)
    - Rental Agreements 120-134, February 1963; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box RG3.1-1998.003, Folder 119)
    - Rental Agreements 135-149, March 1963; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box RG3.1-1998.003, Folder 120)
    - Rental Agreements 150-163 (164 missing), 1963 March-1963 April; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box RG3.1-1998.004, Folder 1)
    - Rental Agreements 165-180, 1963 April-1963 May; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box RG3.1-1998.004, Folder 2)
    - Rental Agreements 180-195, 1963 May-1963 June; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box RG3.1-1998.004, Folder 3)
    - Rental Agreements 196-199, 1963 June; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box RG3.1-1998.004, Folder 4)
    - Rental Agreements 200-209, 1963 June-1963 July; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box RG3.1-1998.004, Folder 5)
    - Rental Agreements 210-219, 1963 July-1963 August; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box RG3.1-1998.004, Folder 6)
    - Rental Agreements 220-229, 1963 September-1963 October; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box RG3.1-1998.004, Folder 7)
    - Rental Agreements 231-244, 1963 October; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box RG3.1-1998.004, Folder 8)
    - Rental Agreements 245-258 (259 missing), 1963 October; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box RG3.1-1998.004, Folder 9)
    - Rental Agreements 260-274, 1963 October-1963 November; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box RG3.1-1998.004, Folder 10)
    - Rental Agreements 275-285, 1963 November; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box RG3.1-1998.004, Folder 11)
    - Rental Agreements 286-299, 1963 November-1963 December; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box RG3.1-1998.004, Folder 12)
    - Rental Agreements [300-330], circa 1964 March-1964 October; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box RG3.1-1998.004, Folder 13)
    - Rental Agreements 331-362, circa 1964 March-1964 October; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box RG3.1-1998.004, Folder 14)
    - Rental Agreements 366-390, circa 1964 March-1964 October; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box RG3.1-1998.004, Folder 15)
    - Rental Agreements 391-400, circa 1964 March-1964 October; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box RG3.1-1998.004, Folder 16)
    - Rental Agreements 401-422, circa 1963 December-1964 March; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box RG3.1-1998.004, Folder 17)
    - Rental Agreements 426-450, circa 1963 December-1964 March; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box RG3.1-1998.004, Folder 18)
    - Rental Agreements 451-475, circa 1963 December-1964 March; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box RG3.1-1998.004, Folder 19)
    - Rental Agreements 476-499, circa 1963 December-1964 March; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box RG3.1-1998.004, Folder 20)
    - Rental Agreements 500-525, circa 1964 March-1965 May; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box RG3.1-1998.004, Folder 21)
    - Rental Agreements 526-549, circa 1964 March-1965 May; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box RG3.1-1998.004, Folder 22)
    - Rental Agreements 551-575, circa 1964 March-1965 May; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box RG3.1-1998.004, Folder 23)
    - Rental Agreements 576-599, circa 1964 March-1965 May; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box RG3.1-1998.004, Folder 24)
    - Rental Agreements 601-624, circa 1965 November-1966 March; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box RG3.1-1998.004, Folder 25)
    - Rental Agreements 629-651, circa 1965 November-1966 March; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box RG3.1-1998.004, Folder 26)
    - Rental Agreements 652-676, circa 1965 November-1966 March; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box RG3.1-1998.004, Folder 27)
    - Rental Agreements 677-700, circa 1965 November-1966 March; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box RG3.1-1998.004, Folder 28)
    - Rental Agreements 703-725, circa 1966 January-1966 May; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box RG3.1-1998.004, Folder 29)
    - Rental Agreements 726-750, circa 1966 January-1966 May; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box RG3.1-1998.004, Folder 30)
    - Rental Agreements 751-774, circa 1966 January-1966 May; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box RG3.1-1998.004, Folder 31)
    - Rental Agreements 775-799, circa 1966 January-1966 May; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box RG3.1-1998.004, Folder 32)
    - Rental Agreements 800-825, circa 1966 May-1966 September; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box RG3.1-1998.004, Folder 33)
    - Rental Agreements 827-850, circa 1966 May-1966 September; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box RG3.1-1998.004, Folder 34)
    - Rental Agreements 851-874, circa 1966 May-1966 September; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box RG3.1-1998.004, Folder 35)
    - Rental Agreements 876-898, circa 1966 May-1966 September; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box RG3.1-1998.004, Folder 36)
    - Rental Agreements 901-913, 1962 March; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box RG3.1-1998.004, Folder 37)
    - Rental Agreements 915-925, 1962 March; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box RG3.1-1998.004, Folder 38)
    - Rental Agreements 926-936, 1962 March-1962 April; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box RG3.1-1998.004, Folder 39)
    - Rental Agreements 937-945, 1962 April-1962 May; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box RG3.1-1998.004, Folder 40)
    - Rental Agreements 946-956, 1962 May-1962 June; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box RG3.1-1998.004, Folder 41)
    - Rental Agreements 957-963 (964 void), 1962 June; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box RG3.1-1998.004, Folder 42)
    - Rental Agreements 965-992 (982 void), 1962 June-1962 September; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box RG3.1-1998.004, Folder 43)
    - Rental Agreements 1001-1025, 1964 September-1964 November; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box RG3.1-1998.004, Folder 44)
    - Rental Agreements 1026-1050, 1964 November-1964 December; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box RG3.1-1998.004, Folder 45)
    - Rental Agreements 1051-1075, 1964 December-1965 January; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box RG3.1-1998.004, Folder 46)
    - Rental Agreements 1076-1099, 1965 January; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box RG3.1-1998.004, Folder 47)
    - Rental Agreements 1100-1125, 1965 January-1965 February; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box RG3.1-1998.004, Folder 48)
    - Rental Agreements 1127-1150, 1965 February-1965 March; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box RG3.1-1998.004, Folder 49)
    - Rental Agreements 1151-1175, 1965 March-1965 April; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box RG3.1-1998.004, Folder 50)
    - Rental Agreements 1176-1200, 1965 April; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box RG3.1-1998.004, Folder 51)
    - Rental Agreements 1402-1425, 1965 July-1965 August; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box RG3.1-1998.004, Folder 52)
    - Rental Agreements 1426-1449, 1965 August-October; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box RG3.1-1998.004, Folder 53)
    - Rental Agreements 1451-1475, 1965 October-1965 November; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box RG3.1-1998.004, Folder 54)
    - Rental Agreements 1476-1499, 1965 October-1965 December; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box RG3.1-1998.005, Folder 1)
    - Rental Agreements 1701-1725, 1966 September-1966 October; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box RG3.1-1998.005, Folder 2)
    - Rental Agreements 1727-1748, 1966 October-1966 November; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box RG3.1-1998.005, Folder 3)
    - Rental Agreements 1756-1775, 1966 November-1966 December; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box RG3.1-1998.005, Folder 4)
    - Rental Agreements 1776-1799, 1967 January; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box RG3.1-1998.005, Folder 5)
    - Rental Agreements 2600-2625, 1970 December; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box RG3.1-1998.005, Folder 6)
    - Rental Agreements 2626-2649, 1970 December-1971 January; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box RG3.1-1998.005, Folder 7)
    - Rental Agreements 2651-2674, 1970 January-1971; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box RG3.1-1998.005, Folder 8)
    - Rental Agreements 2675-2699, 1970 February, 1971 March; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box RG3.1-1998.005, Folder 9)
    - Rental Agreements 2700-2725, 1971 March-1971 April; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box RG3.1-1998.005, Folder 10)
    - Rental Agreements 2726-2753, 1971 April-1971 May; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box RG3.1-1998.005, Folder 11)
    - Rental Agreements 2755-2799, 1971 May-1971 June; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box RG3.1-1998.005, Folder 12)
    - Rental Agreements 2800-2830, 1971 July-1971 August; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box RG3.1-1998.005, Folder 13)
    - Rental Agreements 2831-2860, 1971 August-1971 September; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box RG3.1-1998.005, Folder 14)
    - Rental Agreements 2861-2899, 1971 October-1971 November; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box RG3.1-1998.005, Folder 15)
    - Rental Agreements 2900-2933, 1971 December-1972 January; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box RG3.1-1998.005, Folder 16)
    - Rental Agreements 2934-2966, 1972 January-1972 February; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box RG3.1-1998.005, Folder 17)
    - Rental Agreements 2967-2999, 1972 February-1972 March; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box RG3.1-1998.005, Folder 18)
    - Rental Agreements 3000-3025, 1972 March-1972 May; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box RG3.1-1998.005, Folder 19)
    - Rental Agreements 3026-3050, 1972 May-1972 July; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box RG3.1-1998.005, Folder 20)
    - Rental Agreements 3051-3099, 1972 June-1972 September; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box RG3.1-1998.005, Folder 21)
    - Rental Agreements 3301-3325, 1972 November; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box RG3.1-1998.005, Folder 22)
    - Rental Agreements 3326-3350, 1972 November-1972 December; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box RG3.1-1998.005, Folder 23)
    - Rental Agreements 3351-3390, 1972 December-1973 February; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box RG3.1-1998.005, Folder 24)
  - Corporate rental agreements, 1962-1973; Series 3 Subseries 3
    This subseries contains rental agreements, receipts, and related correspondence from the corporations that used the ARG service for long-term art loans used to decorate their offices.
    - Corporate Rental Agreements: American Petroleum Inst., Undated; Series 3 Subseries 3 (Box RG3.1-1998.005, Folder 25)
    - Corporate Rental Agreements: FDIC Rentals, 1964-1998; Series 3 Subseries 3 (Box RG3.1-1998.005, Folder 26)
    - Corporate Rental Agreements: Geico, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 3 (Box RG3.1-1998.005, Folders 27-28)
    - Corporate Rental Agreements: MCI Corporate Rentals, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 3 (Box RG3.1-1998.005, Folder 29)
    - Corporate Rental Agreements: B.F. Saul Company, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 3 (Box RG3.1-1998.005, Folder 30)
    - Corporate Rental Agreements: Wittenberg Associates, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 3 (Box RG3.1-1998.005, Folder 31)
    - Corporate Rental Agreements: World Bank, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 3 (Box RG3.1-1998.005, Folder 32)
  - Rental returns, 1962-1973; Series 3 Subseries 4
    This subseries contains forms which record the date due on an art work, the renter, the Art Rental number, the date returned, and the fees, if any.
    - Rental Returns, Series 3, Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.005, Folder 33)
  - Rental gallery income, 1962-1973; Series 3 Subseries 5
    This subseries contains the daily breakdown of artworks rented or purchased and the income that was generated from those transactions. The forms include information on date, purchaser/renter, Rental Agreement number, Art Rental number, artists, price, fee, and tax (titles of art works are included on purchaser's list). These records are usually in the form of an itemized, typed list kept by month during any given year, but in cases where there is just a summary income report, the daily rental/purchaser sheets and receipts have been saved.
    - Rental Gallery Income, 1973; Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box RG3.1-1998.005, Folder 34)
    - Rental Gallery Income, 1972; Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box RG3.1-1998.005, Folder 35)
    - Rental Gallery Income, 1971; Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box RG3.1-1998.005, Folder 36)
    - Rental Gallery Income, 1970; Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box RG3.1-1998.005, Folder 37)
    - Rental Gallery Income, 1969; Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box RG3.1-1998.005, Folder 38)
    - Rental Gallery Income, 1968; Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box RG3.1-1998.005, Folder 39)
    - Rental Gallery Income, 1967; Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box RG3.1-1998.005, Folder 40)
    - Rental Gallery Income, 1966; Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box RG3.1-1998.005, Folder 41)
    - Rental Gallery Income, 1965; Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box RG3.1-1998.005, Folder 42)
    - Rental Gallery Income, 1964; Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box RG3.1-1998.005, Folder 43)
    - Rental Gallery Income, 1963; Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box RG3.1-1998.005, Folder 44)
    - Rental Gallery Income, 1962; Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box RG3.1-1998.005, Folder 45)
  - Rental gallery exhibitions and sales, 1962-1973; Series 3 Subseries 6
    This subseries contains correspondence and memos with artists, galleries and exhibition organizers; artists and lists of art works; price lists; and sales receipts.
    - 15th Area Exhibition, 1962 January 19-1962 February 18; Series 3 Subseries 6 (Box RG3.1-1998.005, Folder 46)
    - 16th Area Exhibition, 1963 December 12-1964 February 02; Series 3 Subseries 6 (Box RG3.1-1998.005, Folder 47)
    - 17th Area Exhibition: Sales, 1965; Series 3 Subseries 6 (Box RG3.1-1998.005, Folder 48)
    - 17th Area Exhibition: Correspondence, 1965; Series 3 Subseries 6 (Box RG3.1-1998.005, Folder 49)
    - 29th Biennial: Sales, 1965; Series 3 Subseries 6 (Box RG3.1-1998.006, Folder 1)
    - Biennial Poster Sales: 32nd Biennial, 1971; Series 3 Subseries 6 (Box RG3.1-1998.006, Folder 2)
    - Delaunay: Tapestries and Prints, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 6 (Box RG3.1-1998.006, Folder 3)
    - 11th Area Photographers Show, 1971 April 09; Series 3 Subseries 6 (Box RG3.1-1998.006, Folder 4)
    - Art Rental 5th Anniversary Exhibition, 1967; Series 3 Subseries 6 (Box RG3.1-1998.006, Folder 5)
    - Francis, Sam, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 6 (Box RG3.1-1998.006, Folder 6)
    - Graphics Exhibition and Sales (Women's Committee), 1964; Series 3 Subseries 6 (Box RG3.1-1998.006, Folder 7)
    - Shephen Green Show-Sales, 1963 March 14-1963 April 14; Series 3 Subseries 6 (Box RG3.1-1998.006, Folder 8)
    - Prints from Halifax, 1971; Series 3 Subseries 6 (Box RG3.1-1998.006, Folder 9)
    - Interior Designers- Art Rental Gallery, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 6 (Box RG3.1-1998.006, Folder 10)
    - Japanese Painting Exhibition- Sales, 1964 October; Series 3 Subseries 6 (Box RG3.1-1998.006, Folder 11)
    - Jewelry Show- Fairtree, 1973; Series 3 Subseries 6 (Box RG3.1-1998.006, Folder 12)
    - Sales: Richard LaFean, 1964; Series 3 Subseries 6 (Box RG3.1-1998.006, Folder 13)
    - Sales: Richard Lahey Retro, 1963; Series 3 Subseries 6 (Box RG3.1-1998.006, Folder 14)
    - Sales: 30th Biennial, 1967; Series 3 Subseries 6 (Box RG3.1-1998.006, Folder 15)
    - Feldman Prints- Sales, 1967; Series 3 Subseries 6 (Box RG3.1-1998.006, Folder 16)
    - Harold Isen: Graphics '67, 1967; Series 3 Subseries 6 (Box RG3.1-1998.006, Folder 17)